mature-qualitysingles.com 2016-12-10

# Mature Quality Singles - Privacy Policy

### Effective Date: June 28, 2013

Our postal address is   
**Mature-QualitySingles.com  
15851 Dallas Parkway, Suite 600  
Addison, TX 75001**

We can be reached via e-mail at [privacy@Mature-QualitySingles.com](mailto:privacy@Mature-QualitySingles.com)

Mature-QualitySingles.com is committed to protecting your privacy. We maintain the privacy of your information using security technologies and adhere to policies that prevent unauthorized use of your personal information. This privacy policy may be modified in the future and will be posted on our website.

In addition to the information we collect directly from you, we also monitor and track usage of our website, viewing and traffic patterns, customer behavior, and other similar information. We use this information, as well as all of your personal information, for internal business and administrative purposes to improve our website, our product and service offerings, our operations, and our customer service. We may also use your personal information from time to time to send you special offers, new products, services, promotions, and other similar information.

We are able to offer our services to you, in part, because you agree that such act constitutes a purchase, an inquiry and/or an application for purposes of the Amended Telemarketing Sales Rule, 16 C.F.R. § 310, et seq. (the "ATSR"). Notwithstanding that your telephone number may be listed on the Federal Trade Commission's Do-Not-Call List, you expressly consent to allow Mature-QualitySingles.com to contact you by email, telephone or other means, including contacting you using an automated telephone dialing system, prerecorded message.

The information we collect is used to improve the content of our Web page, to customize the content and/or layout of our page for each individual visitor, to notify consumers about updates to our Web site, to contact consumers for marketing purposes, to share or sell to other reputable organizations to help them contact consumers for marketing purposes.

With respect to cookies: Cookies are small text files that are placed on your computer's hard drive by our computers or servers to identify your computer. Cookies are only read by the server that placed them there and are unable to execute any code or virus. We use cookies to record user-specific information on what pages users access or visit, record past activity at a site in order to provide better service when visitors return to our site, customize Web page content based on visitors' browser type or other information that the visitor sends.

With respect to security: We always use industry-standard encryption technologies when sending and receiving consumer data exchanged with our site. We have appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our site.

From time to time, we make the e-mail addresses of those who access our site available to other reputable organizations whose products or services we think you might find interesting. If you do not want us to share your e-mail address with other companies or organizations, please let us know by writing to us at the above address or sending us an email message to [privacy@Mature-QualitySingles.com](mailto:privacy@Mature-QualitySingles.com). Please include your email address and the words "opt out" in the subject or content field so that we can process your request promptly. We do provide aggregate information about site usage and traffic patterns, stripped of any individual identification, to third parties to comply with various reporting obligations and for business or marketing purposes.

If you supply us with your postal address on-line you may receive mailings from other reputable companies. You may have your name put on our "do-not-share" list by writing to us at the above address. When writing to us make sure to provide us your exact name and address. If you prefer, you can also send an email message to [privacy@Mature-QualitySingles.com](mailto:privacy@Mature-QualitySingles.com). Please include your exact name, mailing address and the words "no mail" in the subject or content field so that we can process your request promptly. We will be sure your name is removed from the list we share with other organizations.

Persons who supply us with their telephone numbers on-line will only receive telephone contact from us with information regarding our service.

To the extent permitted by law, you agree not to bring, join or participate in any class action as to any claim, dispute or controversy you may have against Mature-QualitySingles.com or its employees, officers, directors, assignees and servicers. You agree to the entry of injunctive relief to stop such a lawsuit or to remove yourself as a participant in the suit. This agreement is not a waiver of any of your rights and remedies to pursue a claim individually and not as a class action in binding arbitration as provided above. This agreement not to bring or participate in class action suits is an independent agreement and shall survive the end of your membership. 

If you have further questions regarding our privacy practices, please send email to [privacy@Mature-QualitySingles.com](mailto:privacy@Mature-QualitySingles.com).
